https://www.vansgifts.com/information/privacy-policy.asp

[Skip to Content]
INTRODUCTION
Van's Gifts® ("we" or "us" or "our") respects the privacy of our users ("user" or "you"). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website at https://www.vansgifts.com, including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the "Site"). Please read this privacy policy carefully.
If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the site. By visiting VansGifts.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice and in our Terms of Use.
We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason.
We will alert you about any changes by updating the "Last Updated" date of this Privacy Policy.
Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.
You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.
Does Van's Gifts® Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described in this Privacy Policy.
COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes:
Personal Data
Personally identifiable information, such as your name, shipping address, email address, and telephone number, and demographic information, such as your age, gender, hometown, and interests, that you voluntarily give to us when you register with the Site when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as online chat and message boards. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Site.
Derivative Data
Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site.
Financial Data
Financial information, such as data related to your payment method (e.g. valid credit card number, card brand, expiration date) that we may collect when you purchase, order, return, exchange, or request information about our services from the Site. We store only very limited, if any, financial information that we collect. Otherwise, all financial information is stored by our payment processor, J.P. Morgan Chase Bank, N.A., PayPal, and you are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions.
Data From Social Networks
User information from social networking sites, such as Apple's Game Center, Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest, Twitter, LinkedIn, including your name, your social network username, location, gender, birth date, email address, profile picture, and public data for contacts, if you connect your account to such social networks.
Mobile Device Data
Device information, such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer, and information about the location of your device, if you access the Site from a mobile device.
Third-Party Data
Information from third parties, such as personal information or network friends, if you connect your account to the third party and grant the Site permission to access this information.
Data From Contests, Giveaways, and Surveys
Personal and other information you may provide when entering contests or giveaways and/or responding to surveys.
Where We Store Your Information
Our Service is operated in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to, and stored in, the United States. By using the Service or otherwise providing us with information, you hereby consent to this transfer. At times, for orders originating within the EU or UK or being delivered to the EU or UK, we may use third parties located within the EU or UK to process such orders.
In so doing, we take steps to ensure those entities will process your information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Although personal information collected by us through the Service will be used by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the U.S. may not be as stringent as those in other countries.
How Long We Keep Your Personal Information
We may retain your information in accordance with our data retention policies and for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, or until you request us to stop using it.
We may, however, keep some of your personal information to ensure that we comply with your request not to use your personal information or comply with your right to erasure.
For example, we must keep your request to be erased, even if it includes your personal data, until such time as you are no longer our customer.
If you have questions about our data retention policies, or would like a copy of such, please contact us as noted below.
How Your Information Is Secured
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at Customer Service.
If you place an order on our Website, it encrypts the credit/debit card number you submit prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology through digicert. This technology works best when the website is viewed using Microsoft IE® and Edge®, Google Chrome®, Mozilla Firefox®, and Apple Safari® browsers. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard personal information once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information we receive.
Portions of the Service (such as our Member registration and Address Book) may require registration and log-in processes in which you will select a user ID and password (collectively, the "Password"). Passwords provided to you by us are the confidential property of the Company and may be used by you solely for your individual use of the Service (and otherwise as specified by us). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Password and for all activities that occur using your Password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your Password or accounts.
How To Limit The Use Of Or Modify Your Information
We want to communicate with you only to the extent you want to hear from us.
Any promotional email we send to you (or your gift recipient after consent) will include an "unsubscribe" link to use or a link to opt-out of receiving further promotional emails from the sender.
If you wish to set your preferences concerning promotional communications, or you prefer not to have your personal information shared with third parties, please let us know by contacting us as noted below in the "How to Contact Us" section and identify your preferences regarding promotional communications and the sharing of your contact information. Your instructions will be processed as soon as reasonably practicable and in accordance with law.
What If I Choose Not To Give You My Personal Information
You are not obligated to provide us your personal information.
However, if the personal information is necessary in order to supply goods or services to you under a contract or an order between you and the Company and you do not give us your personal information, then we will not be able to enter into that contract or honor that order for goods or services.
USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience.
Specifically, we may use information collected about you via the Site to:
Email you regarding your account or order.
Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the Site.
Increase the efficiency and operation of the Site.
Monitor and analyze usage and trends to improve your experience with the Site.
Generate a personal profile about you to make future visits to the Site more personalized.
Notify you of updates to the Site.
Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties.
Create and manage your account.
Perform other business activities as needed.
Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal activity.
Process payments and refunds.
Request feedback and contact you about your use of the Site.
Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.
Respond to product and customer service requests.
Administer sweepstakes, promotions, and contests.
Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoena.
Deliver targeted advertising, coupons, newsletters, and other information regarding promotions and the Site to you.
Enable user-to-user communications.
Offer new products, services, and/or recommendations to you.
Send you a newsletter.
Solicit support for the Site.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows:
By Law or to Protect Rights
If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation.
This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Third-Party Service Providers
We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.
Marketing Communications
With your consent, or with an opportunity for you to withdraw consent, we may share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.
Interactions with Other Users
If you interact with other users of the Site, those users may see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity, including sending invitations to other users, chatting with other users, liking posts, following blogs.
Online Postings
When you post comments, contributions, reviews or other content to the Site, your posts may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Site in perpetuity.
Third-Party Advertisers
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site and other websites that are contained in web cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Affiliates
We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.
Business Partners
We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.
Other Third Parties
We may share your information with advertisers and investors for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. We may also share your information with such third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.
Sale or Bankruptcy
If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity.
If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party.
You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy.
We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations.
If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.
TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
Cookies
We may use cookies, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. When you access the Site, your personal information is not collected through the use of tracking technology. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can remove or reject cookies, but be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Site. However, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or by modifying your web browser's settings to notify you each time a cookie is tendered, permitting you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.
We may use cookies, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize, facilitate purchases, manage orders and generally improve your experience on the Site. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by this Cookie Policy.
To not agree to this Cookie Policy may result in a poor experience and/or even break your ability to use the Site.
Internet-Based Advertising
Additionally, we may use third-party software to serve ads on the Site, implement email marketing campaigns, and manage other interactive marketing initiatives.
This third-party software may use cookies or similar tracking technology to help manage and optimize your online experience with us.
For more information about opting-out of interest-based ads, visit the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool(Opens in a new window) or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool(Opens in a new window).
Website Analytics
We may also partner with selected third-party vendors, such as Adobe Analytics/Omniture Site Catalyst(Opens in a new window), Akamai(Opens in a new window), Google Analytics(Opens in a new window), and others, to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyze and track users' use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. This site uses Google Analytics demographic and interest reporting. Click on the following link to learn more about how Google uses this information www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/(Opens in a new window). In addition to other options listed below, click this link for currently available opt-out options(Opens in a new window) from Google Analytics.
By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. However, if you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-party vendor or the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool(Opens in a new window) or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool(Opens in a new window).
You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser's cookies files may also clear certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings and it is the Users responsibility to manage and maintain these.
THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES
The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site.
SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information.
While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.
Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.
POLICY FOR CHILDREN
We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below.
CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected.
No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online.
If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. If you set the DNT signal on your browser, we will respond to such DNT browser signals.
OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION
Account Information
You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by:
Logging into your account settings and updating your account
Contacting us using the contact information provided below
Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.
Emails and Communications
If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:
Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the Site
Logging into your account settings and updating your preferences
Contacting us using the contact information provided below
Using the Unsubscribe link included in our marketing emails
If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Privacy Under Section 1798.83
California Civil Code Section 1798.83(Opens in a new window), also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.
If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Site, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Site. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California.
We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Site, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.
Your California Privacy Rights Under the CCPA
California law permits customers, who are residents of California under Assembly Bill 375(Opens in a new window), to request information about their personal information, if any, which Van's Gifts® discloses to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes.
(We do not currently sell any of our 1st party information to any 3rd parties for their use in anyway.)
To make such a request, or ask any specific question regarding this, please write to us at:
Van's Gifts®
4101 Bonita Place, Suite A
Fullerton, CA 92835
Attn: CA Resident Privacy Request
If you would like to update or correct information previously provided to us, please contact us as indicated below in the "How to Contact Us" section.
Upon your written request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
Members can directly access, modify and update their membership information (including name, mailing address, birth date, telephone number and email address) by accessing the password-protected "Update Membership" page.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
We guarantee your satisfaction. If you or your recipients are not 100% satisfied, simply let us know and we'll make it right!
Shop with confidence
EMAIL SIGN-UP:
Toll Free: (800) 822-7538 | Email: customerservice@vansgifts.com | Address: PO Box 3330, La Habra, CA 90632
©Copyright 2020 Van's Gifts. All Rights Reserved.
This website uses cookies. By using our services, you agree to our use of cookies
More Details
